{"questions":[{"question":"The 9th letter in the Greek alphabet is \"iota\"","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"True","true_false":true},{"content":"False","true_false":false}]},{"question":"\"Lima\" is the capital of Chilli.","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"True","true_false":false},{"content":"False","true_false":true}]},{"question":"\"snake oil\" cures all ills.","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"True","true_false":false},{"content":"False","true_false":true}]},{"question":"The European Union count less or more than 25 countries ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"More","true_false":true},{"content":"Less","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Facebook exist since less or more than 15 years ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"More","true_false":true},{"content":"Less","true_false":false}]},{"question":"German football team wins less or more than 3 times the world cup ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"More","true_false":true},{"content":"Less","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Steven Spielberg has realised less or more than 80 movies ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"More","true_false":true},{"content":"Less","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Dragon Ball Z count less or more than 300 episodes ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"More","true_false":false},{"content":"Less","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Argentina count less / more than 50 million people ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Less","true_false":false},{"content":"More","true_false":true}]},{"question":"New York city count less or more than 10 million people ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"More","true_false":false},{"content":"Less","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Greenland count less or more than 75 000 people ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Less","true_false":false},{"content":"More","true_false":true}]},{"question":"A wild male lion lives less or more than 13 years on average ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"More","true_false":false},{"content":"Less","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Who said : \"The die has been cast\" (Alea jacta est) ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Caesar","true_false":true},{"content":"Winx Club","true_false":false},{"content":"Attila","true_false":false},{"content":"Georges Auguste Escoffier","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Who was the god of war in greek mythology ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Hera","true_false":false},{"content":"Hades","true_false":false},{"content":"Hermes","true_false":false},{"content":"Ares","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Which arctor is the main character in \"Interstellar\" ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Brad Pitt","true_false":false},{"content":"Matthew McConaughey","true_false":true},{"content":"Tom Cruise","true_false":false},{"content":"The Rock","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The number of players side in each side in Water Polo is .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"7","true_false":true},{"content":"9","true_false":false},{"content":"5","true_false":false},{"content":"4","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Who was the architect of North and South Blocks of the Central Secretariat in Delhi ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Sir Edward Lutyens","true_false":false},{"content":"Herbert Baker","true_false":true},{"content":"Antonin Raymond","true_false":false},{"content":"Robert Tor Russell","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The National Police Academy is located at .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Abu Road","true_false":false},{"content":"Hyderadad","true_false":true},{"content":"Bengaluru","true_false":false},{"content":"Dehradun","true_false":false}]},{"question":"In which country is Karabla, the holy city of Shia Muslims located ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Iran","true_false":false},{"content":"Syria","true_false":false},{"content":"Jordan","true_false":false},{"content":"Iraq","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Thomas Cup is associated with .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Hockey","true_false":false},{"content":"Football","true_false":false},{"content":"Badminton","true_false":true},{"content":"Basket Ball","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Eden Garden (Kolkata) is associated with .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Basket Ball","true_false":false},{"content":"Football","true_false":false},{"content":"Criket","true_false":true},{"content":"Hockey","true_false":false}]},{"question":"What is Amnesty International ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"A Peace Movement","true_false":false},{"content":"An Environment Protection Organization","true_false":false},{"content":"A Human Rights Organization","true_false":true},{"content":"An Organization","true_false":false}]},{"question":"2018 FIFA World Cup took place in .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Russia","true_false":true},{"content":"Qatar","true_false":false},{"content":"France","true_false":false},{"content":"Netherlands","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The name of famous clown at Food chain McDonald’s name is .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Ronald McDonald","true_false":true},{"content":"Col. Harland Sanders","true_false":false},{"content":"Asa Candler","true_false":false},{"content":"Ray Kroc","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Bagram is an airbase of USA situated in .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Pakistan","true_false":false},{"content":"Kazakhstan","true_false":false},{"content":"Somalia","true_false":false},{"content":"Afghanistan","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Vatican city in which the Pope lives is a city that lies in .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Belgium","true_false":false},{"content":"France","true_false":false},{"content":"Germany","true_false":false},{"content":"Italy","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Hegel was a ..... Philosopher","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Swedish","true_false":false},{"content":"French","true_false":false},{"content":"Italian","true_false":false},{"content":"German","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Black Pool is a ..... in England","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Resort","true_false":true},{"content":"Hotel","true_false":false},{"content":"Tower","true_false":false},{"content":"Island","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Moseley Road Baths are located in .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Afghanistan","true_false":false},{"content":"Iran","true_false":false},{"content":"UK","true_false":true},{"content":"India","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Pakistan played first test match in .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"1953","true_false":false},{"content":"1954","true_false":false},{"content":"1952","true_false":true},{"content":"1951","true_false":false}]},{"question":"How many High Courts of Pakistan are there ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"4","true_false":false},{"content":"6","true_false":false},{"content":"7","true_false":false},{"content":"5","true_false":true}]},{"question":"SAARC 1st summit was held in .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Mumbai","true_false":false},{"content":"Dhaka","true_false":true},{"content":"Kathmandu","true_false":false},{"content":"Tehran","true_false":false}]},{"question":"World Happiness Index was first time published in year .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"2010","true_false":false},{"content":"2009","true_false":false},{"content":"2013","true_false":false},{"content":"2012","true_false":true}]},{"question":"World Press Freedom Prize was established in ..... by United Nations’ cultural body UNESCO’s","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"1997","true_false":true},{"content":"1999","true_false":false},{"content":"1995","true_false":false},{"content":"1993","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Working boundary is the border between Pakistan and ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Afghanistan","true_false":false},{"content":"Indian-occupied Kashmir","true_false":true},{"content":"India","true_false":false},{"content":"Iran","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Ghana is the new name of ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Silver coast","true_false":false},{"content":"Gold coast","true_false":true},{"content":"Diamond coast","true_false":false},{"content":"Black coast","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Habsha is the old name of ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Zaire","true_false":false},{"content":"Ethiopia","true_false":true},{"content":"Uganda","true_false":false},{"content":"Nigeria","true_false":false}]},{"question":"What is a basin ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"High area of land","true_false":false},{"content":"Deep area of ocean","true_false":false},{"content":"Deep area of River","true_false":false},{"content":"Lower area of land","true_false":true}]},{"question":"The International Anti-Corruption Day (IACD) is observed annually across the world on ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"9th January","true_false":false},{"content":"1st January","true_false":false},{"content":"9th December","true_false":true},{"content":"1st February","true_false":false}]},{"question":"ODI stands for ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"One Day International","true_false":true},{"content":"Oracle Data Integrator","true_false":false},{"content":"Overseas Development Institute","true_false":false},{"content":"Office for Disability Issues","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Battery was invented by ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Nicolas Léonard Sadi Carnot","true_false":false},{"content":"Alessandro Volta","true_false":true},{"content":"Friedrich Bessel","true_false":false},{"content":"Michael Faraday","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Who was known as the “Ambassador to the World’s Religion” ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Huston Smith","true_false":true},{"content":"Mala YousafZaai","true_false":false},{"content":"Dalayi Lama","true_false":false},{"content":"None of these","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Panda is found in which country ? ","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Bhutan","true_false":false},{"content":"China","true_false":true},{"content":"Nepal","true_false":false},{"content":"India","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Helsinki is the capital of which country ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Finland","true_false":true},{"content":"North korea","true_false":false},{"content":"Austria","true_false":false},{"content":"Poland","true_false":false}]},{"question":"South Pole was discovered by ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Robert Peary","true_false":false},{"content":"Cabot","true_false":false},{"content":"Roald Amundsen","true_false":true},{"content":"North America","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The length of USA and Canada border is ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"8891 KM","true_false":true},{"content":"7611 KM","true_false":false},{"content":"5525 KM","true_false":false},{"content":"4278 KM","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The longest border in the world between two countries is ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Radcliffe Line","true_false":false},{"content":"Durand line","true_false":false},{"content":"None","true_false":false},{"content":"International boundary","true_false":true}]},{"question":"The border between USA and Canada is officially known as ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"38 Parallel line","true_false":false},{"content":"International boundary","true_false":true},{"content":"37 Parallel line","true_false":false},{"content":"Hinden berg line","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Which City of UK will host Commonwealth Games 2022 ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Manchester","true_false":false},{"content":"Birmingham","true_false":true},{"content":"None of these","true_false":false},{"content":"London","true_false":false}]},{"question":"In 2018 Commonwealth Games athletes from ..... countries participated ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"75","true_false":false},{"content":"71","true_false":true},{"content":"70","true_false":false},{"content":"72","true_false":false}]},{"question":"2018 Commonwealth Games were held in which Australian city ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Canberra","true_false":false},{"content":"Sidney","true_false":false},{"content":"None","true_false":false},{"content":"Gold Coast","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Where is the Headquarter of Islamic Military Counter Terrorism Coalition (IMCTC) ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"None of Them","true_false":false},{"content":"Jeddah","true_false":false},{"content":"Riyadh","true_false":true},{"content":"Mekkah","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The Islamic Military Counter Terrorism Coalition (IMCTC) is an alliance of how many Islamic countries ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"34","true_false":false},{"content":"53","true_false":false},{"content":"50","true_false":false},{"content":"41","true_false":true}]},{"question":"The Euro currency is used by ..... countries.","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"17","true_false":false},{"content":"19","true_false":true},{"content":"18","true_false":false},{"content":"20","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Riskdag is the name of parliament of ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Denmark","true_false":false},{"content":"Canada","true_false":false},{"content":"Swedish","true_false":true},{"content":"Somalia","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Who has scored the most goals ever in football history ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Pele","true_false":true},{"content":"Zidane","true_false":false},{"content":"Meradona","true_false":false},{"content":"Ronaldo","true_false":false}]},{"question":"“Yusuf Zulekan” is a ..... love Story.","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Urdu","true_false":false},{"content":"Balochi","true_false":false},{"content":"Sindhi","true_false":false},{"content":"Punjabi","true_false":true}]},{"question":"The eradication of poverty day is internationally observed on .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"October 18","true_false":false},{"content":"October 17","true_false":true},{"content":"October 16","true_false":false},{"content":"October 19","true_false":false}]},{"question":"‘Mein Kampf’ is autobiography of ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Navakov","true_false":false},{"content":"Goethe","true_false":false},{"content":"Posternak","true_false":false},{"content":"Adolf Hitler","true_false":true}]},{"question":"International date line passes through which strait ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Java Strait","true_false":false},{"content":"Malacca Strait","true_false":false},{"content":"Adam Strait","true_false":false},{"content":"Bering Strait","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Who is known as Napoleon of Asia ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Tipu Sultan","true_false":false},{"content":"Hemu Bekal","true_false":false},{"content":"Nadir Shah","true_false":true},{"content":"Chandra Bose","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Which poet is called Romi of Kashmir ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Syed Waris Shah","true_false":false},{"content":"Mian Mohammad Bakhsh","true_false":true},{"content":"Syed Bulleh Shah","true_false":false},{"content":"Hashim Shah","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The ..... used in the Construction of the Burj Khalifa weighs the same as five A380 aircraft ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Aluminium","true_false":true},{"content":"Nikal","true_false":false},{"content":"Silver","true_false":false},{"content":"Silicon","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Last specie white Rhino died on ..... in Sudan?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"06 March,2018","true_false":false},{"content":"12 March,2018","true_false":true},{"content":"24 March,2018","true_false":false},{"content":"19 March,2018","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Helvetia is the old name of ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Switzerland","true_false":true},{"content":"Italy","true_false":false},{"content":"Indonesia","true_false":false},{"content":"Veitnam","true_false":false}]},{"question":"What is the longest glacier in the Karakoram and second-longest in the world’s non-polar areas ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Siachen Glacier","true_false":true},{"content":"Sokha Glacier","true_false":false},{"content":"Hispar Glacier","true_false":false},{"content":"Passu Glacier","true_false":false}]},{"question":"What does the Roman Numeral C represents ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"50","true_false":false},{"content":"None of the above","true_false":false},{"content":"100","true_false":true},{"content":"1000","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Commonwealth Secretariat was formed in which year ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"1959","true_false":false},{"content":"1963","true_false":false},{"content":"1965","true_false":true},{"content":"1967","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The highest civil award is ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Nishan-e-Imtiaz","true_false":false},{"content":"Nishan-e-Hyder","true_false":false},{"content":"Nishan-e-Pakistan","true_false":true},{"content":"Nishan-e-Sadarat","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Nabi tajima became the oldest woman in japan in ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"15 September 2013","true_false":false},{"content":"27 September 2015","true_false":true},{"content":"15 September 2014","true_false":false},{"content":"15 September 2012","true_false":false}]},{"question":"World’s oldest person (woman) From japan,was died on 21-april-2018, at the age of 117 was ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Nabi tajima","true_false":true},{"content":"Shazia iqbal","true_false":false},{"content":"Jeane calmete","true_false":false},{"content":"Junko tabie","true_false":false}]},{"question":"World food day is internationally observed on .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"October 18","true_false":false},{"content":"October 19","true_false":false},{"content":"October 17","true_false":false},{"content":"October 16","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Herodotus is called .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Father of Comedy","true_false":false},{"content":"Father of Biology","true_false":false},{"content":"Father of Physics","true_false":false},{"content":"Father of History","true_false":true}]},{"question":"..... book is written on the life of Sir Syed Ahmad Khan.","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Pir-e-Kamil","true_false":false},{"content":"Spirit of Islam","true_false":false},{"content":"Aab-e- Hayat","true_false":false},{"content":"Hayat-e-jawaid","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Al Jazeera TV channel belongs to which country ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Kuwait","true_false":false},{"content":"Qatar","true_false":true},{"content":"Syria","true_false":false},{"content":"Iran","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The world’s largest Cargo aircraft,Antonov AN-225 Mriya, made it’s first landing in karachi for refueling on ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"21 April 2018","true_false":false},{"content":"18 April 2018","true_false":false},{"content":"20 April 2018","true_false":true},{"content":"19 April 2018","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The most salty sea in the wolrd ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Black Sea","true_false":false},{"content":"Dead Sea","true_false":true},{"content":"Arabian Sea","true_false":false},{"content":"Caspian Sea","true_false":false}]},{"question":"World fastest bird is ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Ostrich","true_false":false},{"content":"Peregrine falcon","true_false":true},{"content":"Humming Bird","true_false":false},{"content":"Hen","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Petronas Tower are in ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Colombia","true_false":false},{"content":"Paris","true_false":false},{"content":"Rome","true_false":false},{"content":"Kuala Lumpur","true_false":true}]},{"question":"World book day is celebrated on .... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"22 Apr","true_false":false},{"content":"17 Mar","true_false":false},{"content":"23 Apr","true_false":true},{"content":"21 May","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Non-violence day is internationally observed on .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"October 4","true_false":false},{"content":"October 2","true_false":true},{"content":"October 1","true_false":false},{"content":"October 3","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The depth of the Mariana Trench is ..... meters.","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"10,994","true_false":true},{"content":"10,411","true_false":false},{"content":"10,611","true_false":false},{"content":"10,011","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The Engadin Valley is located in: ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Portugal","true_false":false},{"content":"Turkey","true_false":false},{"content":"Switzerland","true_false":true},{"content":"Egypt","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Lake Lucerne that has complicated shape with several sharp bends and four arms is located in:","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Switzerland","true_false":true},{"content":"Turkey","true_false":false},{"content":"Egypt","true_false":false},{"content":"Portugal","true_false":false}]},{"question":"NPT stands for ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"National Protection Treaty","true_false":false},{"content":"Non-Resident Protection Treaty","true_false":false},{"content":"Non-Poliferation Treaty","true_false":true},{"content":"National Purification Treaty","true_false":false}]},{"question":"What is the Capital of Ecuador ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Quito","true_false":true},{"content":"Islamabad","true_false":false},{"content":"Maxico","true_false":false},{"content":"Dehli","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The Capital Asset Pricing model calculate expected investment ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Risk","true_false":false},{"content":"Return","true_false":false},{"content":"None of the above","true_false":false},{"content":"Risk and Return","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Rawal Dam is constructed on which river ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Chenab river","true_false":false},{"content":"Kabul river","true_false":false},{"content":"Indus river","true_false":false},{"content":"Kurrange river","true_false":true}]},{"question":"What is the power capacity of Diamer Bhasha Dam ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"5400 MW","true_false":false},{"content":"4500 MW","true_false":true},{"content":"4000 MW","true_false":false},{"content":"5000 MW","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Who is the Father of Communism ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Alfred Marshell","true_false":false},{"content":"Adam Smith","true_false":false},{"content":"Karl Marx","true_false":true},{"content":"Arestotle","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The stone age people had the first domestic ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"dogs","true_false":false},{"content":"horses","true_false":false},{"content":"asses","true_false":false},{"content":"sheep","true_false":true}]},{"question":"The Sinai Peninsula is located in:","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Portugal","true_false":false},{"content":"Switzerland","true_false":false},{"content":"Turkey","true_false":false},{"content":"Egypt","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Twitter was created by:","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"All Above","true_false":true},{"content":"Jack Dorsey","true_false":false},{"content":"Noah Glass","true_false":false},{"content":"Biz Stone","true_false":false}]},{"question":"World’s tallest tree is known as ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Basswood","true_false":false},{"content":"Redwood","true_false":true},{"content":"Hawthorn","true_false":false},{"content":"Yellow Birch","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The first artificial satellite on earth is  ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Prithvi","true_false":false},{"content":"Sputnik I.","true_false":true},{"content":"Gaia","true_false":false},{"content":"Giotto","true_false":false}]},{"question":"CTBT was adopted by the UN General Assembly on ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"12 September, 1995","true_false":false},{"content":"24 September, 1996","true_false":true},{"content":"18 September, 1998","true_false":false},{"content":"13 September, 1997","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Capital of East Timor ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Sydney","true_false":false},{"content":"Dili","true_false":true},{"content":"Helsinki","true_false":false},{"content":"Beirut","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Who said “Better to reign in hell than serve in heaven” ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Sadam hussain","true_false":false},{"content":"Bush","true_false":false},{"content":"Hitler","true_false":false},{"content":"Milton","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Name the Powerful Country which offered help to the Pakistan Army before surrendering in Dhaka during 1971 war ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"United kingdom","true_false":false},{"content":"France","true_false":false},{"content":"United States","true_false":true},{"content":"Russia","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The name United nations was adopted at the suggestion of .....","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Stalin","true_false":false},{"content":"Chrchill","true_false":false},{"content":"Roosevelt","true_false":true},{"content":"George Degual","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Who was known as “Man of Destiny” ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Musolini","true_false":false},{"content":"Napoleon","true_false":true},{"content":"Nehru","true_false":false},{"content":"Hitler","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Glucose syrup is made from ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"rice","true_false":false},{"content":"wheat","true_false":false},{"content":"maize","true_false":true},{"content":"oat","true_false":false}]},{"question":"When did Facebook go public ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"May 18, 2012","true_false":true},{"content":"April 15, 2012","true_false":false},{"content":"December 28, 2012","true_false":false},{"content":"July 11, 2012","true_false":false}]},{"question":"When Facebook launched ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"March 2004","true_false":false},{"content":"April 2004","true_false":false},{"content":"January 2004","true_false":false},{"content":"February 2004","true_false":true}]},{"question":"In 1999, the Melissa virus was a widely publicized: ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Trojan horse","true_false":false},{"content":"E-mail virus","true_false":true},{"content":"Macro virus","true_false":false},{"content":"Time bomb","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Who invented bulb ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Willium","true_false":false},{"content":"Robert","true_false":false},{"content":"Philips","true_false":false},{"content":"Edison","true_false":true}]},{"question":"According to the latest WHO 2015 Report, What is the average age of Pakistan ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"66.4","true_false":true},{"content":"50.4","true_false":false},{"content":"45.2","true_false":false},{"content":"55.3","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The world’s most famous physicist, Stephen Hawking has ..... children’s ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"3","true_false":true},{"content":"1","true_false":false},{"content":"5","true_false":false},{"content":"4","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Headquarters of Interpol is located in ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"London, UK","true_false":false},{"content":"Vienna, Austria","true_false":false},{"content":"Lyon, France","true_false":true},{"content":"New york, USA","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Swat Valley is situated in the mountain range of ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"None of the above","true_false":false},{"content":"Himalayas","true_false":false},{"content":"Hindukush","true_false":true},{"content":"Karakorum","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Cyprus is an island in the ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"South China Sea","true_false":false},{"content":"Red Sea","true_false":false},{"content":"Caribbean Sea","true_false":false},{"content":"Mediterranean Sea","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Bering Strait separates Asia from ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"None of the above one","true_false":false},{"content":"Africa","true_false":false},{"content":"America","true_false":true},{"content":"Australia","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Alexandria is a seaport of ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Germany","true_false":false},{"content":"Iran","true_false":false},{"content":"Greece","true_false":false},{"content":"Egypt","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Red sea is between ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Arabia and Africa","true_false":true},{"content":"China and Japan","true_false":false},{"content":"Germany and Scandinavia","true_false":false},{"content":"Turkey and Russia","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Sea of Japan’ is famous for ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Mineral Water","true_false":false},{"content":"Icebergs in water","true_false":false},{"content":"Fishing Area","true_false":true},{"content":"Oil Reserves","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Thai airway is the airline of ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Singapore","true_false":false},{"content":"USA","true_false":false},{"content":"Thailand","true_false":true},{"content":"China","true_false":false}]},{"question":"How many Pakistani blue helmets have embraced martyrdom while serving under the UN umbrella ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"160","true_false":false},{"content":"156","true_false":true},{"content":"165","true_false":false},{"content":"150","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Quaid-e-Azam first wife died in ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"1894","true_false":false},{"content":"1893","true_false":true},{"content":"1895","true_false":false},{"content":"1896","true_false":false}]},{"question":"United Nations University lies in ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Switzerland","true_false":false},{"content":"U.S","true_false":false},{"content":"Colombia","true_false":false},{"content":"Japan","true_false":true}]},{"question":"NEQS refer to ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Upper atmosphere","true_false":false},{"content":"Sea- bed","true_false":false},{"content":"Environment","true_false":true},{"content":"Continental shelf","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The fastest marine animal found in warmer parts of five oceans of the world  ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Sailfish","true_false":true},{"content":"Tunny","true_false":false},{"content":"Wahoo","true_false":false},{"content":"Marlin","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Name the World’s Largest cruise ship ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Harmony of the Seas","true_false":false},{"content":"Oasis of The Seas","true_false":false},{"content":"Symphony of the Seas","true_false":true},{"content":"Allure of the Seas","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Which is the world’s tallest lighthouse ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Baishamen Lighthouse","true_false":false},{"content":"Jeddah Light","true_false":true},{"content":"Ile Vierge Lighthouse","true_false":false},{"content":"Alexandria Light","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Which Chief Justice of Pakistan died in office, 9 days after taking oath ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Sir Abdul Rashid","true_false":false},{"content":"Mohammad Haleem","true_false":false},{"content":"Iftikhar Muhammad Chaudhry","true_false":false},{"content":"Muhammad Shahabuddin","true_false":true}]},{"question":"..... was the first wife of Quaid-e-Azam?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Sakshi bai","true_false":false},{"content":"None","true_false":false},{"content":"Emibai","true_false":true},{"content":"Ratan bai","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Border line which separates outer space from Earth’s atmosphere is known as ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Durand line","true_false":false},{"content":"Venus line","true_false":false},{"content":"Karman line","true_false":true},{"content":"Space line","true_false":false}]},{"question":"“Shining Path” is a militant group of which country ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Mexico","true_false":false},{"content":"Peru","true_false":true},{"content":"Bolivia","true_false":false},{"content":"Paraguay","true_false":false}]},{"question":"White river is located in ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"South Africa","true_false":false},{"content":"China","true_false":false},{"content":"U.S","true_false":true},{"content":"Austria","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The world’s oldest parliament, founded in the year 930 AD is ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Diet of Japan","true_false":false},{"content":"Althing of Iceland","true_false":true},{"content":"British Parliament","true_false":false},{"content":"Cortes of Spain","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Blue River is located in ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"China","true_false":false},{"content":"South Africa","true_false":false},{"content":"Austria","true_false":false},{"content":"U.S","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Yellow river is located in ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Austria","true_false":false},{"content":"China","true_false":true},{"content":"South Africa","true_false":false},{"content":"U.S","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Green river is located in ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"South Africa","true_false":false},{"content":"U.S","true_false":true},{"content":"China","true_false":false},{"content":"Austria","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The Amazon river dolphins is also called ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Green river dolphins","true_false":false},{"content":"White river dolphins","true_false":false},{"content":"Blue river dolphins","true_false":false},{"content":"Pink river dolphins","true_false":true}]},{"question":"The Black river is located in ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Jamaica","true_false":true},{"content":"Canada","true_false":false},{"content":"Argentina","true_false":false},{"content":"Chile","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Headquarter of the African Union is located in ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Dakar","true_false":false},{"content":"Cairo","true_false":false},{"content":"Johannesburg","true_false":false},{"content":"Addis Ababa","true_false":true}]},{"question":"How many states are in Europe ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"49","true_false":false},{"content":"48","true_false":false},{"content":"47","true_false":false},{"content":"50","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Pakistan Television started in the reign of ...... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Ayub Khan","true_false":true},{"content":"Zulfiqar Ali Bhutto","true_false":false},{"content":"Yahya Khan","true_false":false},{"content":"Zia Ul Haq","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The UN official birthday is celebrated on ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"October 24, 1945","true_false":true},{"content":" November 24, 1945","true_false":false},{"content":"September 24, 1945","true_false":false},{"content":"December 24, 1945","true_false":false}]},{"question":"How many official working languages recognized by UN (United Nations) ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"4","true_false":false},{"content":"6","true_false":true},{"content":"5","true_false":false},{"content":"7","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The General Assembly of UN meets regularly once a year on third Tuesday of ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"December","true_false":false},{"content":"October","true_false":false},{"content":"September","true_false":true},{"content":"November","true_false":false}]},{"question":"Total number UN Security Council members is ..... ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"20","true_false":false},{"content":"10","true_false":false},{"content":"15","true_false":true},{"content":"5","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The oldest anthem of the world is ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Denmark anthem","true_false":false},{"content":"Japan anthem","true_false":true},{"content":"China anthem","true_false":false},{"content":"Russia anthem","true_false":false}]},{"question":"The oldest flag of the world is ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Japan","true_false":false},{"content":"China","true_false":false},{"content":"Greece","true_false":false},{"content":"Denmark","true_false":true}]},{"question":"Harrapa city is situated on the bank of which river ?","sip":3,"answers":[{"content":"Chenab","true_false":false},{"content":"Sutlej","true_false":false},{"content":"Indus","true_false":false},{"content":"Ravi","true_false":true}]}]}